### Julia Alonso Martínez

Project Manager



Valencia, Spain

#### Contact

Phone number: +31 630 22 18 22

Email: alonsomartinezjulia.1988@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/julia-alonso-martínez-13828b128

## **Summary**

"Watch the little things; a small leak will sink a great ship" - Benjamin Franklin.

I am a passionate project manager certified by the Project Management Institute (PMI), Scrum.org and Google. My mission is to plan and supervise projects to ensure they are completed timely, within planned resources and budget.

I have more than six years of experience in customer service, administration and troubleshooting positions. This has allowed me to develop a strong sense of responsibility, organization and empathy towards the client and my colleagues.

I obtained my BA in History at the University of Valencia. City where I studied Spanish sign language interpretation. After years of working with clients, I decided to specialize in project management and obtain the professional certificate in project management from Google, the certified associate in project management (CAPM) from the Project Management Institute (PMI), and the Professional Scrum Master I (PSM I) certification from Scrum.org.

I'm always interested in hearing from former colleagues, managers, or just interesting creative people, so feel free to contact me if you'd like to connect.

# **Professional Experience**

•	05/2022 – Present	Project Manager Freelance (self-employed)
•	07/2021 – 12/2021	Administrative Salesperson Gana Energía
•	06/2017 – 07/2021	Specialist agent in telephone customer service Atento España
•	12/2015 – 05/2017	Agent in telephone customer service Atento España

#### **Education**

- 2013 2015 **Higher Education Training Cycle. Sign Language Interpretation** CIFP Misericordia. Valencia, Spain
- 2006 2011 Bachelor of Arts (BA), History Specialty in Ancient History Universitat de València. Valencia, Spain

#### Licenses and certifications

- Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM)
   Project Management Institute. July 2022
- Professional Scrum Master I (PSM I)
   Scrum.org. July 2022
- OKR Certified Professional OKRCP CertiProf. Professional Knowledge. August 2022
- Foundations of Digital Marketing and E-commerce
   Google Coursera. August 2022
- Agile with Atlassian Jira Atlassian. June 2022

- Google Project Management Six-course Professional Certificate Google – Coursera. May 2022
- Digitization applied to the productive sector CEPYME. December 2021

#### Courses

- OKR Goal Setting: The Complete Guide to OKRs Udemy
- Professional English for customer service Servef
- Library and Archives Technician IVEP

## Languages

- **German** A1 Level of the Common European Framework Reference for Languages (CEFR). German Center (Centro Alemán). July 2017
- Cambridge First Certificate in English (FCE) B2 level of the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages (CEFR). 2016
- Intermediate Grade in Valencian Level C1 of the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages. (CEFR). 2014